flora2000.com 2018-06-28

# Privacy Policy - Flora2000

Overview  
Orios Ltd. is committed to keeping our customers informed about how we use the information we gather from you through the use of our website www.flora2000.com.

Please read this privacy policy ("Policy") carefully to understand how we will use and protect your personal information. We will not share your personal information with anyone except as described in this Policy. Questions regarding this Policy should be directed to support@flora2000.com or we may also be contacted directly at the following address:  
Orios Limited  
Suite 3,  
Watergardens Block 4,  
Gibraltar - Europe 

What information do we collect? -We collect certain personal information about you - but only when that information is provided by you or is obtained by us with your authorization. We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, use our reminder service or subscribe to our newsletter or Fleur Privileges Program. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. We may ask you to provide your date of birth, anniversary date of you, a friend, a loved one, family members or other third parties, and certain holiday information that may reveal one's religious background, so that we may send them or you an email, hint or reminder about an event that could be made more special with the gift of our products. You may also visit our site anonymously. 

We may also collect non-personal information such as the website's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address 

What do we use your information for?  -Our main aim in collecting information is to enhance our customers' shopping experience. Among other things, we use customer contact information in the following ways: \- To personalize your experience Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs. \- To improve our website We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. We collect certain information from visitors while shopping on our Sites for the purposes of system administration, to gather broad demographic information, and to monitor the level of activity on our Sites. \- To improve customer service Your information helps us to effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. If you use our Order Enquiry service we will gather your email address and account password, if you have one, in order to locate your order so that we may give our most recent tracking information. We also use your information to trace false orders, to remind customers of events through our reminder service(s), and to send service emails, newsletters, and promotional emails from us or third parties. You can opt out of our newsletters or decide the frequency of the same. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties? \- As a general rule, we do not disclose personal information about our customers to anyone - we are the sole entity viewing your information. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance \- As we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into My Account and editing the details there or by emailing us at support@flora2000.com. 

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  \- We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

Your Consent \- By using our site or obtaining any product or service through our site, you agree to the collection and use of information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Policy is incorporated into, and considered part of, our Terms and Conditions. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy \- Any change, modification, addition or removal of portions of this Policy will be posted on this page. Please be sure to check this page before proceeding to use our site. 

Contacting Us -Thank you for allowing us to serve your gifting needs. We value your business and are committed to protecting your privacy. We hope you view our company as a trusted service provider and we will work to continue earning your trust. Please call us if you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or if we can be of further service.

You may contact us using the information below:  
support@flora2000.com  
1800 456 1797
